Adrian Gift

Adriangift@yahoo.com

To: **HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGER**

Objective: Seeking an opportunity for employment with a major Company

To Whom It May Concern:

My name is Adrian Gift; I have 10 years of experience working in the service industry, having held positions as Sales Representative, Store Manager, Restaurant/Bar Manager, Security Supervisor and bartender. These roles have involved staff supervisor, motivating support staff, inventory control, payroll data, daily cash reconciliation, merchandising and assisting customer with product which, as result, led to high sales for the company. I am able to offer you knowledge and experience in these areas.

In addition, I have extensive integrated knowledge about interacting with clients, peers and other supervisors; resolving conflict situations; managing time; marketing and sales; communication both verbal and written as well as delivering an exceptional level of customer service and satisfaction.

I am therefore seeking a position with your company that would allow me to contribute to the business and would welcome the opportunity to develop a career in your organization as well as help you attain your corporate objectives.

Attached is my resume that highlights my education and work experience.

I look forward to your favorable reply and the opportunity for an interview to discuss employment with your company.

Yours Sincerely,

Adrian Gift

ADRIAN GIFT

Address: # 121Diego Martin Main Rd., Diego Martin, Trinidad W.I.
Phone: 312-0066/389-9281

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

More than 10 years of successful experience in direct sales of a range of products and services.

Exceptional talent in handling inquiries and persuasive in sales for products and services.

Excellent communication skills either written or verbal.

Extensive practical hand-on experience as co-owner of a home base business.

Motivated and enthusiastic about developing good relations with clients.

Effective working alone or as a cooperative team member.

Professional in appearance and presentation.

RELEVANT SKILLS

Sales:

Able to comfort dissatisfied customers, settle them and provide resolution. Effectively increased customer sales in various positions. Prepare sales report, purchase orders and conduct regular inventory. Extensive experience in direct sales of products and services.

Customer Relations:

Coordinate the issue of product information, delivery of product and after sales service for major accounts. Promote product at trade show. Handle face-to-face and phone contact with new and established customers.

Advertising, Marketing & Distribution:

Organized and styled merchandise for effective presentation in store. Kept accurate, current records of inventory and suppliers. Handle all aspects of order taking and processing.

Management & Supervision:

Perform all aspects of operating a small business as co-owner. Responsible of training numerous new employees in several situations and supervise employees. Able to develop rapport in work environment that builds teamwork. Responsible for handling large amount of cash, use of cash register and preparation of back deposits. Producing payroll data

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Store Manager

Linda's Bakery – St James branch (June 2014 – present)

General Manager/Owner

Mr. Gift Catering & Bar services (2008 – Present) Management of Catering and Bar service for events.

Sales Representative

In Style Patio
Angelina St., St. James (2010)
Sales Representative and Administrative Support

Restaurant & Bar Manager

Martin's on the Boulevard (1998 – 2009)

#13 Cipriani Boulevard, P.O.S. Management of bar and restaurant staff. Inventory control and management. Ensure customer service and satisfaction. Administrative Support

Senior Supervisor

Protective Agencies Ltd. St. James (2004 – 2005)

Personnel Supervision. Control of Incidents and events. Ensure that staff and client adhere to security policies and practices

Store Manager

Katbiji (1999 – 2002)

Espermaria Plaza, Henry Street P.O.S.

Supervision of store staff. Inventory control. Receipt and maintenance of stock. Producing payroll data. Ensure customer service and satisfaction. Cash management.

Store Manager

Brasil Italia (1995 – 1999)

#41, Frederick Street, P.O.S.

Supervision of store staff. Inventory control. *Customer* service. Producing payroll data. Ensure *customer* service and satisfaction. Daily cash *reconciliation*

EDUCATION

1979-1982 Gower House School, Blackbird Cross, London, England.

1979-1982 Archbishop Carroll High School Washington D.C. U.S.A.
 1984-1986 St. Bede's High School, (the Dicker), Sussex, England
 1986-1987 Daniel Progressive Institute, POS, Trinidad

FURTHER PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Defensive Driving

Radio Broadcasting.

Basic use of Microsoft Office and Internet.

Land Mark Forum Education – a transformational course focusing on personal ans professional relationship and development.

Hotel Management School: Tourism Management course, 50% completed.

REFERENCES

Jason Clarke / 474-2050 Martin Baptiste / 623-7632 Euard Williams / 625-2601

OTHER INFORMATION

Driver's Permit, Class 3, Issue date 29-02-2008 Suzuki APV Minivan, 7 seats, 2010 year.